One hundred and thirty two years.
Destiny had been waiting...
For this to happen.
Our love will be rewritten on the
day of the fourth chance.
Shae needs to know
that I'm having fun too
and my weekend's not boring.
Guys!
Sorry.
Were you hurt?
Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
Shae... James confessed to me.
He said I'm the one he likes.
I only have James.
So, don't take him away.
James... I already told you
to stop bugging me.
Hey...
- No, please go.
- Come on. Let's go.
Hey!
Ouch!
This is not your diary.
And it will never be yours.
Huh?!
How did you--
You were just there moments ago.
We should hurry!
What happened to you?
Are you hurt?
Why is your nose bleeding?
This is a prank, right?
My schoolmates are making fun of me again.
Tell them this is getting too old now.
Don't fool me or else...
And where did you learn that language?
Forgive her.
She might be tired from studying last night
- That's why she's acting strange.
- She called me Carmelita?
My ancestor? Oh no, is this a
side effect from the sleeping pills?
Helena, Nenita, Natasha... You go ahead.
I will take her to the
convent to get some rest.
Wait... Hold on!
Carmelita!
Come back here!
Wait!
So, I went back to the time of Carmelita?
I-- I think I'm gonna die!
Okay. I'm dead.
Miss?
Dad?
Carmelita?
How are you feeling?
Gosh. I'm still here?
I am not dreaming?
This is real. This is so real.
I've sent a letter to Mother and Father.
I'm sure you'll be able
to come home safely.
What?
We're sisters?
Ofcourse!
What are you talking about, Carmelita?
It is I, your sister Josefina.
Josefina? The one Grandma Carmina talked
about. Carmelita's sister who became a nun.
My gosh. I need to go back home.
How can I return home?
Where am I? What is this place?!
I cannot understand you. We're
here at Colegio de Santa Isabel!
You have to bring me back
to the place where you found me!
I want to go back home!
What is happening to you?
Carmelita!
Please, help me!
I don't care how high this is, I will jump!
Carmelita!
- Carmelita, will you lie down?!
- I want to go home! Daddy!
- What's wrong with you?
- Daddy! Daddy, help me! No!
What is happening to you?
You are not making any sense!
Please! I need to get out of here!
Carmelita, calm down.
How dare you?!
Demon, begone from our sister's body!
Natasha, what are you doing?
Your sister is being possessed, Josefina!
- I'm not possessed...
- She's speaking another language.
Can't you hear what she's saying?
She doesn't recognize you
and she's saying she's not Carmelita.
I bid you, demon.
Leave our sister's body! Help me out here!
Let us pray!
Hail Mary, full of grace.
The Lord is with you.
Blessed are you--
Let her go.
Mother Olivia!
You...
It's you...
It's you!
What's wrong with all of you?!
Leave us alone.
Can you please explain to me?
First, you stole my diary.
Second, you took me into this place.
And now, they're thinking
that I am possessed.
I want to go home.
I want to go home!
First and foremost...
I didn't stole the diary.
I am going to return it to its true owner.
Second...
I was not the one who brought you here.
And third...
You are the reason
Why they assumed
you are being possessed by a demon.
Okay...
Fine.
Whatever.
But I want to go home now.
How can I go back?
There is no other way
back to your own time...
Unless you finish your mission here.
Mission?
What mission?
You have to stop destiny.
You have to change what was written there.
You and Juanito may never be together.
You have to stop him
from falling in love with you.
You cannot fall in love
with him in order to...
Save him from being murdered
on the day of your wedding.
She drowned herself in the lake.
Annoying!
She killed herself because of a broken
heart and now I'm tangled up in their mess?
What if I refuse?
What if I just admit to them that
I am not Carmelita?
That I'm from the future.
Alright...
It's up to you.
Let us see if they will believe you.
There can only be two possibilities.
First...
They may believe that
you are being possessed.
Or maybe...
They may believe you have lost your mind.
They may take you to all sorts of healers.
Until they leave you for
good in a far off island.
Why is there no good choice?
The moment that happens...
You will lose the chance
to go back to your time.
Hold on to this.
You are now it's rightful owner.
In nomine Patris, et Fili,
et Spiritus Sancti. Amen.
I prayed for Carmelita to the Virgin Mary.
I hope she'll get better soon.
That's right.
Whatever is happening to Carmelita now...
I'm sure she'll get passed it.
Thank you, Helena, Nenita.
I'm glad Carmelita has friends like you.
Let us hurry. It is time to prepare dinner.
More things were written here before.
Where are they?
For now, nothing is written there.
We are in the time of June 1891.
What?
We're just in June right now?
But Juanito died on February 29, right?...
It means I have to stay for seven months
in order to finish my mission?
That's too long.
You and Juanito cannot meet each other yet.
But...
He has already laid his eyes upon you.
He saw me... But I didn't see him?
What do you mean?
He saved you earlier this morning.
When do I meet him?
He's heading here right now.
What?! As is now?! Now already?!
Mother Olivia. Mr. Juanito
Alfonso is waiting downstairs.
He wants to check on Miss Carmelita.
Tell him to come back another day.
Carmelita is not feeling
well at the moment.
What?
But I'm feeling fine.
I want to see Juanito. We need to talk.
It cannot be.
You still need to explain
yourself to the women
who saw you. Tell them
you are not possessed.
Go to sleep.
Think hard about your mission.
Where have you been, Nenita?
Have you forgotten about your chores?
I just opened the door for
the gentleman who visited.
You know it is not allowed to accept
guests in the convent at this late hour.
Poor Juanito.
Did you say Juanito?
It seems like he's worried about
Carmelita. That's why he came.
He might just wanted to check on her.
If that's the case,
then I hope he can give us an answer
as to why my sister is acting strangely.
May the Lord bless him.
Will I really be staying here?
No electricity.
No cellphone.
No internet! No wi-fi!
I can't stay here!
I need to find a way to escape from here.
So, I just need to
keep Juanito from falling
in love with me to
stop him from dying?
That's easy. Why don't I just talk
to him directly so I can warn him?
I just wanted to check how
she's doing, Mother Olivia.
She might have other symptoms
from what happened earlier.
That's Juanito? The man I need to save?
I can't see his face,
but... he has nice body.
Don't you worry...
Señor Hidalgo gave me permission since
this is part of my studies in medicine.
Thank you for your concern, Juanito.
But I have to disappoint you.
Carmelita decided to rest early.
I'll go ahead. Please be on your way.
Sampaguita!
Oh God, please get away, dog!
Don't be loud! The thief may fall down!
Me? A thief?
Hi, it's me. Carmela who became
Carmelita Montecarlos of 1891.
Locking eyes with the man who
shattered her heart into pieces.
And broke her will to live after
her beloved was murdered.
Are you sure Carmelita will
be just fine, Mother Olivia?
Please excuse my worrying heart.
She is very precious to
our Mother and Father.
She's the youngest of our family.
Carmelita is a quiet and reserved lady.
If given the chance, they wouldn't
want to be parted away from her.
But she was allowed to study here
in Manila because I am here with her.
I don't want to disappoint my parents.
She'll get back to how
she was before, Josefina.
I'll look after her.
Do not worry, Miss.
I'll catch you if you fall.
I don't believe in love at first
sight. I don't believe in forever either.
I don't even believe in
happy endings. But now...
Why do I feel like I want
to get shot by Cupid?
Miss!
Ouch!
Are you hurt anywhere?
Isn't it obvious?
What are you doing up there?
I'm a thief just like what
you said earlier, remember?
I thought men in this era were gentlemen.
Do you really have no
intention of helping me?
But, Miss, I can't be just careless
with my actions and touch you.
Ah, right. People were more
conservative back in the old days.
Who's out there?
Come quick!
Who are you?
Let's go! Carry me.
Who's out there?
Take me there! Carry me, quickly!
Quick! You have to carry me!
There! Over there!
- Juanito, quickly!
- Alright, alright!
We almost got caught.
Wait, Miss...
How did you know my name?
Juanito.
Listen carefully to what I'm about to say.
This man's a snob.
Okay, fine. Fine.
One of the nuns told me that you were here.
She spoke your name.
That's how I knew.
But that's not important.
Juanito...
Whatever happens...
Don't you dare fall in love with me.
In love?
Right. People here aren't
used to speaking English yet.
What I meant was...
You must not give your heart to me.
Why...
Why are you laughing?
Miss... please don't take it the wrong way.
But the truth is, my heart
already belongs to someone else.
What?! I got rejected?!
Is there anyone there?
Who's out there?
Sampaguita!
Juanito, dear.
- Mother Olivia.
- What are you still doing here?
I'm just looking for my dog, Sampaguita.
Sampaguita!
Sampaguita! Sampaguita!
Where did you go?
You must be on your
way, dear. It's getting late.
Yes, Mother Olivia.
Thank you.
Come now, Sampaguita.
Always keep this in mind.
Alright. Until our next class.
- Umm...
- Juanito.
How was your excursion last night?
Did you examine the injured lady?
There was no dizziness or confusion.
Nor slowness in her responses or lethargy.
The lady is in good health.
Good.
I believe you'll become an
exceptional doctor, Juanito.
I'd like to ask permission, Doctor.
To be excused from
our class for a few days.
My Father and Mother are
asking me to come home.
No problem.
Are you coming back to San Alfonso?
Yes.
Gracias, Señor.
Carmelita, take a bath and get dressed.
Where are we going?
We're going home to San Alfonso.
Don't worry. I won't
tell them what you did.
I was the only one who saw
you and Juanito last night.
I thought you were never
going to forget Leandro.
Wasn't he the reason you
wanted to come here with me?
Leandro?
What a funny thing, love.
One can never be sure when
it will fall into someone new.
Are you ready?
Our chauffeur is alreay here.
You're coming with us?
I won't allow you to mess up
what is destined to happened
That is why I'm coming
to keep an eye on you.
I can do it.
I'm a strong, independent woman.
I'm sure he'll keep his distance from
me since I was too aggressive last night.
But that's good so he'll never be
linked to Carmelita now.
It seems like you're writing
all your woes in that diary.
You shouldn't have done that.
What did I do wrong?
You shouldn't have met with him last night.
How did Mother Olivia
knew that I met Juanito?
You cannot hide anything from me, Carmela.
Why did you push me into
the Arc of the Centuries?
It was painful and I tripped as well.
Dear, you must learn how
to be polite with your words.
Being respectful and having good manners
are important in this time period.
Of course. But why did you push me?
You still shouldn't have
met Juanito last night.
Expect that a lot of things that are
supposed to happen will now change.
And because of what you did,
your mission has become more difficult.
Yes, Mother Olivia.
It's been days since I
time slipped into this era.
Get ready. They're already here.
Is Mother Olivia a magician?
She's so good at appearing out of nowhere.
- Carmelita!
- Maria!
- Madre Olivia.
- How are you?
Madre Olivia, did my
sisters give you trouble?
I didn't have any problems with Josefina.
She's diligent in her studies
and is an obedient lady.
Carmelita on the other hand...
Is kind and is also obedient.
Carmelita's reputation is good.
Oh God, I hope I don't ruin it.
My great great great grandmother
is standing right in front of me!
She's so beautiful! Flawless skin and soft
eyes. In short, she's prettier than me.
Carmelita, aren't you glad
to see your eldest sister?
It's been six months since I last saw you.
I'm glad you're back home.
She's so sweet!
It made me remember Jenny and Emily.
I wonder if they're looking for me?
Are they worried about me?
Where are Mother and Father, by the way?
They're preparing for the festival.
Father has a lot of visitors today.
They're waiting for us at the house.
Come now. The carriage is waiting.
Maria...
I'd like to take Carmelita with me.
There's something we've got to go first.
Is that so?
Josefina and I will run along then.
Good idea.
I will have Eduardo escort you.
My butt hurts from seating
too long in the carriage.
That is why we rest before moving on.
Be careful, dear.
Carmela, dear.
Don't forget that you are
Carmelita while you are here.
Yeah, it's fine, Mother. Don't worry...
Our names sound the exactly the same, so...
I can handle it.
Dear,..
fix the way you talk.
People in this time
period don't talk that way.
Aside from that,
mind your actions. Don't
be unrefined or rowdy.
Maybe I shouldn't move at all?
You know, dear.
During this time...
Women are...
very conservative.
They do not hold hands.
And they do not look into the eyes of men
who aren't their partners.
Remember that.
- Eduardo.
- Yes?
Return to our carriage
and keep an eye on our belongings.
Thank you.
Dear. All that your eyes can reach
is owned by the Montecarlos family.
Wow!
Happy festivities, Mother Olivia.
Happy festivities to you as well, Raul.
Where are you headed?
To the preparations for
the Thanksgiving Feast.
- Good. Take care, Raul.
- You as well.
Dear,
he is the father of Eduardo.
He's been serving the Hacienda
Montecarlos for a long time.
Your crops are the main products
sold by San Alfonso to Manila.
That is why your family is
one of the riches in this town.
Wow...
That is the Lake of Tears
that is connected to the Wailing River.
Lake?...
Wait... Lake of Tears? Isn't that the...
That is indeed the lake
where Carmelita drowned herself.
The real Carmelita.
Gosh! Someone died there!
I'm losing it!
Mother Olivia, Miss.
We need to go now.
Alright.
OMG! This is the same as
Grandma Carmina's house!
But bigger, newer, and more elegant!
Seems only yesterday that I've been here.
Remember.
They must not suspect
that you are not Carmelita.
Our most beloved youngest daughter.
Carmelita. Thank goodness
you came back safe and sound.
- Come on.
- Let's head inside.
This way.
- You look like you enjoyed your travels.
- How was your trip?
My god! What will I do now?
So they're Carmelita's parent's then.
Don Alejandro, and Doña
Soledad Montecarlos.
Please take some rest.
We're heading to
the Alfonsos for dinner.
Mother Olivia, aren't we
going to eat? I'm so hungry.
The mass earlier was too long
and I can't even understand a thing
since it's in Latin and Spanish!
Dear,
learn how to speak
respectfully to your elders.
You will be scolded by anyone if
they hear you speak like that.
- Amigo!
- Don Mariano!
We were a bit early.
I don't intend to keep you waiting,
but our dinner will be served shortly.
He is the Governor of San Alfonso.
And beside him is his wife,
Doña Juanita.
And his right hand man,
Captain Corpuz.
Now, I'm delighted to introduce
you to my children.
Who bring us both joy and pride.
- This is Sergio.
- Sergio.
- This is Angelito.
- Angelito.
And of course...
Juanito!
My god!
Juanito?
Juanito?!
Juanito.
Thank you, mother.
Eat up.
My gosh.
I forgot that he was the Governor's son.
I shouldn't have come here.
I'm remembering all the silly things I did!
Miss!
Juanito.
- What's wrong?
- What happened?
- Something's under the table!
- What? What's happening?
Wait.
What's happening?
Sampaguita!
Were you bitten?
- What happened to you?
- Juanito!
- I'm fine.
Dear, are you sure you're alright?
Yes, Don Marino...
I mean, Don Mariano.
I'm fine now.
Doña Juanita,
Don Mariano, I apologize but
it seems like
Carmelita was unharmed.
Good. What's important is that
Carmelita was not hurt.
If that's the case, then
let's continue with our dinner.
- Sit down, everyone.
- Very well.
Take your seats.
Seems like you enjoyed the food
that was served to us.
It was good.
Miss, this is for you.
What's that?
Just like before,
if Father or Mother asks,
you know nothing.
Remember. I covered
up for you and Leandro too.
Again? Who's that Leandro anyway?
I'm heading out.
If Father asks, I'm in the bathroom.
My beloved,
I am now here at our meeting place.
Under the mango tree that
has been a witness to our love.
I am waiting to see your beauty
that is unmatched in this world,
now and forever.
Beauty that is
unmatched in this world?
Why?
Have you seen the whole world?
The one who wrote this
is such a sweet talker.
Why do we need to worry about rebels?
Amigo...
As the Gobernadorcillo,
I'm doing the best I can to listen
to every citizen's voice.
I want to make sure to hear all
their worries and needs.
That is why San Alfonso is very fortunate
to have you as our Gobernadorcillo
Right you are, Captain Corpuz.
I saw his care for the people
during our time together at school.
My family...
founded San Alfonso.
That's why this town
is very important to me.
Your dedication is inspiring.
As you are, Alejandro.
Your family business has
indeed grew more profitable.
And you have helped so many people.
You know the hardships
my family faced, Mariano.
I've told you that.
I do not want my family's effort
to be wasted nor our name to be tarnished.
That is why I want
my daughters to marry
into respectable families.
Cheers.
We're fine there at the convent.
All right, I'll go ahead.
They look so happy.
My family is also like this
when we get-together.
How are they doing now?
I'm sure they're worried sick about me.
Carmelita.
Where is Maria?
The thing is...
Is he with Eduardo?!
She met with Eduardo?!
Our servant? He's the one
writing to Maria?
Hush your voice or
someone might hear you!
Oh! For real?
Listen to me.
We're about to go home.
Find Maria and tell her to come back
before Father looks for her.
I will buy you some time.
Why don't we just
tell them the truth?
They'll bound to find out anyway.
That cannot be.
Father might kill Eduardo!
You know that Eduardo
came from a poor family.
Father will never approve
of their relationship.
Go on. Look for her
before anything bad happens.
Alright.
- Where will I look for her?
- Miss?
Miss!
Where do you think you're going?
His tummy really stands out!
if only there were
probiotics around this time.
I just want some fresh air.
Right.
You may not.
What?
You may not do so.
Even if I'm with her?
Dear Diary, what the hell
is he doing here again?
Why do we keep crossing each other's paths?
Is he doing this or is it destiny?
I cannot allow this to continue.
I have to stay away from him, or else,
I won't be able to go back to my own time.
Losing my mind,
Carmela.
Miss.
Where’s the mango
tree around here?
Are we leaving?
Where is your brother?
Where is Carmelita?
You know the saying,
that when something
truly shameful happens,
it’s better to just think
as if nothing happened.
Does it mean something else?
Your secret meetings
with Carmelita?
Carmelita!
Young lady.
You’re going to be late
for the early mass in town.
Is this a joke?
They say she was caught last night
with the youngest of the Montecarlos.
What is this rumor that
you are meeting another?
Juanito, I believe that you have
no relation with Miss Carmelita.
She wants you to clear
her daughter’s name.
My friend, I would like to propose
that the wedding be held
at the end of February
for the young ones.
What do you say,
Miss Carmelita?
What is it, Doña Juanita?
How many children
do you wish to bear?